bitcasino.io 2019-03-30

# Bitcasino Privacy Policy

_Updated: 24.05.2018_  

Bitcasino (the Company) take protecting your privacy very seriously.  

We implement suitable technical and administrative controls in our endeavours to keep your personal information protected at all times. Our Privacy Policy lays out how your personal information is handled. We ask that you please read through it, as by using our services you agree to accept the terms.  

Personal Information is any information that allows you to be identified and may include your name and address, date of birth, payment details and any other information you may wish to provide or that is collected about you. We will take measures to ensure that use of your Personal Information is compliant with data protection and privacy regulations valid in the countries where we operate. This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information we collect when you use our websites or when you otherwise interact with us.  

The controller of the personal data is mBet Solutions N.V.

## Purpose for the collection of personal data

Your personal information is collected and used for the following reasons:

  * To provide you with our services
  * To make more of such services available to you where possible and appropriate
  * Setting up and managing your account
  * For the purposes of security and control
  * To satisfy regulatory and legal requirements
  * For historical and statistical purposes
  * To notify you about updates to our software or services.

We may further use your personal information in order to contact you from time to time, to introduce you to our products or any events, activities, projects, plans, developments, undertakings and special offers that are taking place, being promoted or supported by the Company. We may contact you via email, live chat or internal support ticket.

When you supply us with your personal information, you are agreeing that you do not consider our use of such personal information - in accordance with this Privacy Policy - as any breach of your rights under the Data Protection Act (Governed by the law of Curacao).

At any time, you have the right to opt out from receiving any promotional and/or marketing materials that we may send you. You are encouraged to contact us should you wish to do so.

## Disclosing personal information to third parties

The Company policy is that your personal information will not be disclosed to anyone other than employees of the Company that require access to your data in order to provide you with a service, with the exception where the Company may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information to relevant authorities.

However, we may disclose Personal Information to government institutions if it is required by law.

## Protection of your personal information

The Company employs physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the security of the data you provide to us. SSL encryption is used on our Website for all sensitive data. The Company advises you to take any and all precautions you can to protect your personal data while using the Internet.

Personal Information will be kept as long as the data is needed to provide the services and stipulated by the law. The customer has the right to ask for Personal Information to be deleted, however, in some cases we may refuse to delete data based on the law.

Should the aim of processing of Personal Information data change, we will inform you as soon as possible. Should there be a need for consent from customers, we will acquire that from you accordingly.

## Access to your personal information

You have the right to access any information we hold about you at any time. You can log in to our Website using your username and password at any time and review your Account page. You can also update or edit your information from this page. You may also contact the company service department at the Company and ask for details of any information we hold about you. You have the right to request any incorrect information to be corrected, or where applicable, removed. The Company reserves the right to ask you for a written request for any information we hold about you.

## Cookies

A cookie is a data packet which is used solely for web analytic purposes. Our Website uses cookies to recognise visitors and facilitate the login process. Cookies used by the Company are only set if the user agrees, and expire within a maximum of four weeks.

## Privacy Commitment

In order to ensure that your personal information remains confidential, our privacy guidelines are communicated to every employee of the Company. Where the Website of the Company contains links to other sites, the Company does not share your personal information with those sites and is in no way responsible for the privacy policies of those sites. We would advise you to make yourself aware of the privacy policies of any such site. If our privacy policy changes and we plan to use your personal information in a way that is different from that stated to you at the time of collection, you will be informed accordingly.

The Privacy Policy of the Company is subject to change at any time and it is advised that you review the Privacy Policy periodically to check for changes.
